hua hai
[music]
photo good evening and good day everyone welcome
to the scientific live episode of visit this
great to have you all with me
2010 annual function which will take questions
from the comments posted in umar 10
min me isko kisi vax udit harshit 2.0
abhishek pawan siddu jitesh udit sharma harish chandra arya
dungar singh chouhan shyam rajendra dilraj shubham ritesh sharma devendra srishti siddhanta
arthik kheda aman arora manjeet singh sagar das gupta
vijay vaghela
and lots of people deepti mishra ashish and
every sense good evening good very great you
all
office game show without any father chit-chat
let's get right in do the questions tak
goodbye and
question number one is by ravindra kumar
according to which side breaths better
ussr usa in cold war invite dasha
is back to show what are your views on this was
expecting a
good
thing i will  Say More Superior
Question
What is the definition of but what is the
best All
posts by benaami2000
Hussaini Nice Good Person But in 0.3 Good
Bye Others on Right or Wrong
No Moral Moral Inferior Only Thing Which
Defines a Good One Side That Policy Studies
in Tractors Pair is on the Back Side
[Music]
Click the Subscribe Button
Subscribe for Seven
Just
History Question Quite
Good Enough Bye Lotus Stands Alone
People to the Right of the Top Did Not Believe in the
Spirit This City and the
End Policies and Myths and Socialism and Marxism
Foreign
Policy New
Century Doing Everything You Need to the
Top Right or Wrong They Are Just
from A to
Z
Subscribe Friends Video
Press
Subscribe Note Communication Duo and This
Android Something Not Want in Line with the
Official Tainted Politicians Not Active of
Your Country Today Due to Somerfield
Id Would this Video
Subscribe Video
not be great
lines of this opposition of modal logic will
decide what is the new norm in India
was
certainly not just the
president of india daily life
india during this period clear
arvind se number sim that don't like vinod how bad
india growth nehru vishwanath 2%
1% person per year a the country developing
countries should grow 100 every one you get their
policies right but india is and without and 109
post
mediocrity 226 indian indian leaders who
dab
school in
this question on ha
and according to electric cars eco
friendly and true sense iron sensing
footprints on electric is the real challenge
fossil fuels generate electricity even
singapore and middle-east debt lifestyle
and moon in favor of mars transit
hydrogen
fifty shades and significances of
electric car serving west side and
which was see electric cars are very good
conduct after thing is under sunshine beach if
government run on lithium-ion battery is  the
synonyms back to back the gautam buddha's adat
ka
decision is like and when scooter number of
kilometers se zyada number
to
subscribe to that
inside complete dip press
performing electric car developed even know
you are that big boss carpet
electricity the electricity is is
generated by burning coal which is horrible
for environment in our country lakhan bhaiya move into
a sustainable fuel sustainable energy
west india is the winner of the solar
alarms movement in india has gone into its already in the
process of moving in a
massive way solar panel renewal for sustainable
energy
power plant
in
electricity from
the
vid oo i
want sunil electric ka adat is line
viewers
bill ab in andhero me electricity to be
connected to sources of power in the
richest
man of the
world
means
subscribe solution
subscribe like sid comes to you want to generate
power
generate electricity water water
water
and electricity
educational developed coming on the same day
deposit war n  Generating hydrogen and
carbon footprint like friends delivered
and fight for all about how are you
generating electricity that is the main
issue from generating electricity the real
goal from solar in day hydrogen will
also be created nor benefit and details
like are you will run will also be cleared
this will also have very low carbon
footprint
best solution you can do it this master at
large country like India and USA
today every one in a lifestyle thing
finally Bigg Boss it is
nonsense to avoid all it is a terrible horrible
subscribe
rooms in everything but still alive to avoid
1978 centuries Indian
cities have not entered different oil mostly I know
dadi smart city things going on
water awwal status of terrorism terrorism
progress cigarette beedi cigarette and off but
legacy systems and British Raj country sesame and
plant Dubey British plant benefits
left 2465 mushrooming of yours with no
planning and  If you want to on
actual in such a tell you can spend two hours
transitive verbs in back home rule of
every year in education
in India will not be electric
subscribe
for India does the the
solution is mask give
quality of world class mass transit
system directly
2012 and
minute
means
the problem
ka solution for
this clearly
speed rail network in the
world
with clean energy
person
click
cheer over Chinese settings open show held were
complex issue but in the solution
Ramesh ko strange how are you generating
electricity
water works for generating electricity
subscribe
The
Amazing se half developed country is the
means of the industry don't
forget to subscribe world top 10
top 10 world to stop stop stop stop stop stop stop
in India it has top six reactions boil
GDP but unfortunately India population
in Jalandhar hour Africa a is
dynasty one India will have population log
gandhi inter-continental of ka beautiful on
GDP per capita most successful test india
reliance communications private
nursing staff 21 countries by GDP per capita
deoal highly industrialized
industries exports friends
manufacture things right left over the top
20 overall countries by oil GDP even when you
will serve form is highly
industrialized
mature industries now in place for very long
time jobs in the flavor
distribution properly deposited
selected in the wake of second world war
between new ki Bigg Boss fir usme
Nagasaki and definitely beautiful Ashish within a couple
of decades and a victim the biggest
technological advances nation on the planet which is
still alive today but its highly
industrialized it is fixed pre mature
in this peace and not developed country it becomes developed
without industry
vidmate app
that shows and which country the list of
industries and the country will achieve its
capital on  Income countries non-completion 17
2010 have a lower levels of
industrialization with the answer is very simple
and a wholesome in developed countries india
news on vitamin industrialization it means develop
invest in its own
industries in technology look at the time
in india was the most developed
civilization in human history which month of
india history is a white last 100 years
and
width top to all of you in your textbook
far present split india was the most
industrialized in the world in the
sub-continent spinning indigenous
industries demonstrator advance
industries all diamond tilak time we met the
best in largest ships in the world which
made the best schools in the world indian
steel sector which
notification a
quality mask real steel and skill that was
invented in india in northern
india and even in n in violation sri lanka
about
₹500
subscribe now to receive new updates
time to
the most  Industrialized Countries and
Most Technologically Advanced Country in the
World
Subscribe to the channel
Number One
Media
Services
in the field of
light turn on
Narcissus India needs industrialization
Indian historian industry life but
technological super power and log in This can happen next
twenty years with right things should
understand me 4a
A R Rahman's special you talk about winning
sanskritam national language and devotion of
years including button caster oil grease
another service sector liquid in IT sector half bus
killed in English speaking population
tennis to visit in English know how to do
and job how to increase pet prayers will
answer
industrialization Indian should come into
industrial super power house and spirit
manufacturing technological super power
in English today if given
58 table exam posts
560 was one of the biggest technological super powers with
hot English look at India on has been in
English to become a technological and
industries super power India was the
greatest he India has to highest GDP
in the history of the world  in english
dashrath has ko and nation can never destroy
high income and mili connection on the basis of
wide service is the nation
has decided bakuli work pdf books and you will become
great nation by babu700
india has to be comment industrial
relation and technological super power
industrial super power deaths have really in
physics look examples from his rib
cage his located in korea located in tigers
look at the chinese how did you low side
middle-income this jo ribbon hi nigam ne
vulgar industrialization not be
provided service to the people sarwan
singh police not avoid it is only one who will win
in
english
subscribe and subscribe the
statement india has always been
technological super power and industry in
india
honey english without english to and
knowledge in three years into all is well and
everyone right to visit to an increase and
gdp 100 percent
places in a
small village
today big
city
subscribe
indian school
girls are
built in a
way  which will be
constructed a
big bee
if profit from water will not see change the
time and labor productivity of money are they
living
things in your life
time if you get then
please
please change your mind
particular
subscribe setting
on
voice
mail listen
Akbar Akbar DNA test mein Swapan
Gwalior mein multiple comfortable pathetic
Ireland in the Bering Strait one drops
connection very good look good very good mein aa
such ita that at r people come from a
little pathetic island in the Bering Strait
next point Veda is Ireland is morning is in
the Bering Strait now this hair pack rope
mouse pointer is the Bering Sea s wearing this
year brings it is this little
children between Alaska and Siberia
and distant most part brush or tilak
tips
ko agar deposit
zoom in this they regret
president Bering Strait this name aa
share the the the the the the the the
people from this place
subscribe to that and expected you
indigenous method the people of this region the
Bering Strait people were last seen people the people
of  Rahu
Saturn Mercury tenth house and take this is actually quite
similar tests where our ancestors come
from
and DNA test is that serious Mongolian
inspiration is not surprised whatsoever
developed lock pattern Gorgia base Mongol year
it's over his wife is well Bering
Strait you most force quick measurement
distance apart play 50 km
Vinod
Mundhra daughter and a son
that a huge research
Gomes pet in this world who married people
moved around returning while gathering in wedding
Roman Empire 200 price in India and
remind
269 depend mother
please look at home with tak problem
Siberia and logic your
means the sentence of the Black Pearl panel
spent in Alaska in North America and
including Greenland school I
am
subscribing and to
one so is much surprised and have
generated with activities peroxide remember
to Mongolian
and even seen theres American people this
Video subscribe
with people  Of
fertile and click to
subscribe of
the story of the
story the
difference
between the people of North America
and observe
and people of
90 tips and
very interesting stories and will benefit who
is more genetic research is done welcome very
interesting judgment
and pride of British rule was
only India partition in
two
years
for the
share
and share
the United Kingdom
is Ireland Ireland
Ireland political
share is Northern Ireland means Sampo
partition on
that British Detroit mix door-to-door on
homeland
partition Ireland Ireland is not a
destination is not English
inter Ireland Ireland
divide divide
and rule
policy of divide next door in the
16th
trees plants interactivity prosperity I don't
country-wide Hindus are brothers and
sisters and
Central and Northern Ireland under
British occupation and Northern Ireland
Ireland is The Independent
subscribe found that
Ireland
BDO came British and English
under for even today
only India
but for
North Korea South Korea
512 the the
Germany just partition involved
persons  including completing it's not only
India the British Partition 21.50 settlement
length hai
that
Akshay El Nino Krishna
Adhir
Withdrawal Par Oxygen Animals And
Birds Play
Subscribe
Norms B.Com 200 Million Years Or More Than One
Million Years Ago That Woh Milne Nahi Bas
Kameez Aur Giraya Is Baar Two Hundred Million
Years Instead Detain At Sixty Five
Million Years From Today Gifted With
Interactive And Destroyed With
Most Likely Not Only In
President David Warner Bigg Boss
Million Years Long You Can
Subscribe
Most Obscure
Only
If You Liked The Video Then
Subscribe To Hai
Otherwise Again Tips Back Defined And
Lad Speech Will Find Some Small Ones Will Be
Preserved In Area That Pharaoh Is
Android 2015 With Wings In Place Of Birds If It's
Not About Animals Typically What You
Rent From The Power Fuel
Smart
Subscribe The Channel Please
subscribe our Channel subscribe
our Channel Mode Switch  of birth was not a
member in the
liberation of
cyanobacteria the
two sides increase the production of oxygen
that lead to what is known as the great
oxygenation events of oxygen test
pimples which the first monthly station check
planet so much oxygen producers guild
of almost all life because oxygen is the
point for regional office suite defense for
some life forms for pimples in even for
victims of opposition in hell for long
periods of
person
unemployed
70%
finger se z f
that saudi arabia 10 most important that his only about
22% oxygen so am a
krishna das ki crop i10
problem win elections for
flowering vs
hemoglobin boys in muffled inhale to our
respiration underfoot to make more
and animals can understand it's
not video co relation
between environment
and large animals that even schwarz fell co  Do
n't forget to subscribe as well as
life forms on point
loot monalisa stone se tea banane grade
291 singh live video sanshak with question
skoda please explain me koi specific
jangid wwe teachers se discover devotion
bada good explain akadan point wah in which
language ok 10000 in this distinction
fantastic very good number hai prasiddh saath na
dhan things and so complex this account is simply cannot be
explained in layman language
person language so let's place something simply cannot be explained
without
mathematical equations this is aimed at isme bhi samjhha
debit the
subscribe mathematical equations and
subscribe code
rustom sale special dimension one time
definition of wedges pe
ki susheel speed of light in this time the then
you must be together the give the invention
of
length obscene but rather much time it is for
Dimensional coordinate system
accident and time do
not forget to subscribe and
subscribe
definitely
use iss deal se ki
speed hai aur sunao
hai and raghav sir and house with india
relaxed to china of profit hai na
website show how strong with chinese army
is when in reality vinod a question is very difficult
for all android app for
prohibition element which not ever for to under estimate adversary
esi dispensary diner very very vik on that
this look at the an
official announcement
home ministry to join us at least three
times in the budget hai
woh more resources in india they have in
modern age a
sezession of
technology ke
half hour this time dashrath twenty first
century it is not long and deep
1971 your physical strength and bravery
and inspires me third which physical college
method today it is all about technology dhun hi dhund we
fighter planes of what sort of
satellite technology this thank  You can not afford to avoid this
you are
new technological advances in
Indian army on resources pm mode the
mez pay in some cases
where is
subscribe machinery hai
and this fee no conflict debut
experience we fighting india and
indian army which waste deposit and
travels polish now this plenty of animals
with and without country in all 9 countries
today indian army is luhar did in group
this
every soldier moral advantage
passed in for mother
research indian soldier is certainly superior as a
person company chinese soldier indian
soldiers of physical this clear without red if
chinese soldiers have seen are not the
videos of world class ninth class
pujan and net
slow
but this research professor and very
important i don't know
* and two ek lesson ko Indore ki special
pure use every resources and means of
disposal sudhar different android use
lofer the researchers say what fear has
propagated boyfriend channel very good
Payment voucher use actors aishwarya when will
expose na research in the video dhdhe
release deposit stunt in which actress
plate soldiers in the recent click by
chinese uses of gautam 720 account died but
they
rather have been exposed sudheer
and
subscribe
quality products video channel
subscribe money to make a video showing
quit wah shoulder sir yes guddu
technologies hi powerful and army air force ne beech wali don
21 a
playlist cost nothing
indian government has immeasurable funds disposal
of the
wind fuel lakhs use million rupees
every month
making good videos a different religious
and social media the what did not want
with you and why they should react they can be more
proactive fennel instead when a video
dhdhe indian lovers must give some pictures
of the indian soldiers more powerful region which wich
ice cream that occupied
softwares painting with significant a
Meaning of this propaganda unites
a news date of fact minds of
people because ordinary people don't know the
difficult thing in the voice of instead Jasbir
with its an can live with
this significant this video social media
twitter instagram facebook app
provides for professional native with due to
affliction arya samaj
click singh dhami
on karo ok baby bar it ganguly to on air
port and always shine of this journey china
typing and capturing tips lekar june
udaipur road connectivity to foist 100 feet is
desh lado fennel buffets source of will
strong and registered a case against a
look at Gujarat
hai so what is chicken 1 june ki siliguri
corridor and here so Siliguri is currently
under the state of husband for
android windows
improvement jo ling siliguri authorise and the
next station of best deals on Samsung J1
so it's for ninth ke famous hai is
About 5 kilometer wide 80 roast point
according to this brinjal jo hai
subscribe according to this Nepal
possibly a place with Chinese President
of
India North East India Company
Robert
Gibbs I am very serious this supreme kiss
India has sufficient for edification android
and employment in rhythm to
previous definition of threat from China you
understand few days back to take care of these
Chinese misadventures ribbon target Chinese
infrastructure insignificant but really
interested in Pacific is this mark noticed
Twitter developed after diploma in
irrigation is own details with good at it's
not the
best information not made public offices
will not quite beneficial deployment
here but it's controlled hypothetical
scenario in which 40 we have succeeded in
capturing this region and cutting of India has
access to the forest of India watch window
with activation seems like a Chinese man
for quite a few years back  in the me come true
Bhutan and desh mein hi one comes through
Nepal in time nobody cares about yato
nishcharti sperm donation will do not overrate
required is this China Azamgarh ritual and
Nepal to de mein hi one comes through Nepali
story and modern history
and difficult of this region
rights watch ne Delhi answer is very simple in that
Sachin has punch to reconnect with North
East different wicket se Bigg Boss
Bangladesh why help Bangladesh warranty
right with strong nation one million reward
of what will give the territory but in the
fields present
rights in times we how to write a
required to hell with spoon sovereignty ko bhi on
racing event to and it access
your territory and will have sufficient amount
for its diplomats in this is the rate of
India this in his regions that office please
go through brinjal simple will take over the
northern part of Bangladesh and water and
nutrition is  Tactically easier to robbers in this
guy and portray improvement in this region
and wicket se Bigg Boss that gas for sometime
we Borneo territory ko police for not too long
and wicket and water crisis is very
simple but it is not aware of being given this thing happen on ho chuke hain
that Aditya Sindhu point this has been you have been saying
later this for
democracy is not suitable for India
video.com India should look back to the
times of India most days  Welcome to our Planet
and
understand what were the causes of India
being highly developed
for the
time
being and inspiration and finally Bigg
Boss something similar
first century hr
subscribe for democracy and see the
result
of 10th class for
unity
centre
subscribe to
loot jao vinod situation in various states
of India will have this larger in other
states oil technicals but you have attacked
India is vivek nation today soft state it is
not of strong state district
magistrate and country to external
forces who work in the country point
considerations the times in programs tours
engineer demographics of India the
influence of and
and it is all thanks to India's which is called
democracy which
puts that in
context of India's modern
democracy being saint louis basic right
its freedom of expression
expressing support for Indians animals
and support for the breakup of India is
freedom of expression and engaging in
Various activities but
definitely not active reengineering India's
demographics and destroying India's
sculptures at all comes under
freedom of expression freedom of speech and
democratic right in
the name of the
ko whatsapp imo any actress now show
VS India stand those years should have lots of
different forms of governance a
good day systems were certain point
system which terrible things at times in some places in
some parts of Indian porn
person frigate the Mauryan time which
every android
interview is democracy in the local
residents of India but also had answer
republic republic in which you have a
king and elected by the people in the
recent
questions page elected by the people and
for the people who want to
two things were
elected
president of
India
in the day achhi to in seventh century in one
go demonstration kar pradesh pradhan bank account
this proof century and two of complete
Anarchy and was called mucho billof
bash at small fish deposit in people
died of the people of Andhra Pradesh in the
mid parking
went to find great world
subscribe to the channel
if
you liked The
Video
subscribe Video
rule
Indian for laughter protest hybrid system this thing
and dimple raw material understand well but once again
the king of temperature was bound to
follow you to himself Delhi president rule in the
name of the people and to carry out the will of the people who did not give
laws will also be noted that India will
observe and not for imposition of India should consider the
law of
conservation of India and Indian
Independence Act to avoid all the
best say people ki
dukaan double left over leader directly
without due to prime minister will be only electrolyte
local representative
will help in this regard and decide
what is the prime minister of
India
subscribe directly Play Services
subscribe Indian hidden
subscribe India Today media very
great
Indian media corrupt
Media media on behalf of system and politicians on
Thursday the
prince of tort video kar bright
student centre - Arvind change a
little
by
solving leaders can
wrestle system in flute ringtone reforms
in india so desperately needs are
your a what is baikunt judge how
different physical and
psychological impact withdrawal after its ok
land acquisition psychological impact is
anant choudhary is a what is 50 length lineal
descendant
and below sleep
lokayukta n that is
lok ke details in your body
examine them
every cell of ginger
that bristle has nucleus except red
blood cells red blood cells nuclear ok dasha have something called
nuclear research
centre in new delhi on complaints of the
human genome ujjain to one comes from your
father mother
difference between that
person
vitamins and physical
genetic code is page 223
subscribe zones in which year the the the the the the that and
others where the
real leader comes from health genetic
code  is included in web in case of
microbes males that is genetic
information that comes from youth will
influence on father usan
speed most wanted to victims of
identification no one comes to off the record
mitochondrial dna with support from
mother's day offspring you male address females
have mitochondrial dna in
mitochondria intercell
but only help ke paas this onto the
offspring a
147 lineages password per mother daughter ki 121
measurements vatvriksha not passed but yaar
seriously password barfi barfi mein is
updater matrilineal
lingeshwar dna genetic information in
quality mitochondrial dna is what
makes up your and matrilineal dna
linear jis water retention scariest
details after death and matrilineal you guys
rup weeks related family wich ghee
verification speed originated from one and
system this factory near yes you guys hussain
Matrilineal you people Hussain you also have
equal nuclear deal and autosomal DNA
which all different kinda toh that is
bacterial DNA giving leaves and
matrilineal Delhi me is ava
psychological impact has nothing will
answer your genetic have some really have seen that can be
scientifically but this apne bal do exactly
decode how adv that surgical
strike office tonic physical height maximum
potential that you can see hidden in a
positive way can right side hai that
notification
middle aged active life style and mid day will
reach your genetic maximum inter physics
lab school included in apples whichever comes
from both sides of events
included but arre not just all the best all a wise
hum countries till hai dekhiye aap
england aisa hai fact what benefit
and how to make officially for preparation
for
100 countries will have The Channel Please
subscribe and subscribe and
subscribe the Channel and
subscribe
the Channel and
subscribe the Channel
subscribe for and of New Zealand
subscribe The Channel
it is so cold who settled and goodbye
English what is this what will take subscribe
to my channel
directly
from the Independent Country Monitoring System
subscribe
button
video
continuation of England Australia and
New Zealand
Australia is
invalid and occupied by the people of
British English
side
subscribe and
support Hussain New Zealand is been
taken or in this point by people of
English and aspirations points 1461
cc
nothing but
colony hue
England ne servi servi doobi
doobi of but how to
make the queen of the
people like to know what
is the full form
of you the
people of users with fear the
consequences of not apologise Singh
a batsman apologises and fourth coming
love you understand there means apologises happen when there's
hot power on display a a
big stick on display not power really
doing man bagging in all the plot size no
problem
and
Subscribe
subscribe Indian
nation with real
power which will not to
transform into power
airplane mode of * happen when everybody will
approach to India as a
superpower without you
android reforms needed
to
subscribe under consideration of
institutions and their political interference in the country in the
so
subscribe thank you
my voice to western dubai still
continuing colonialism in these investment
retailers ramesh yadav s2u
call with appointments significance in the
previous question how to make poll has
ended on withdraw this point to service
lord of foreign affairs in india which
indian service is fully aware of this hai
where sunidhi
ngos in india which have seen millions of
bunrs on foreign funds diverted for
religious organizations zara very
interested in india jaipur in billions of
dollars every year in to india into
constructing a and  Reliance
infrastructure network power structures
today night day now NGOs think tanks and
what not spoil
point colleges in India heralds
them system to interfere in government
of India * * * 1st Indian government
doing things you so much for international
look at with
Indian
gas
learn local the
signs and symptoms and all around you
mother who also in Odisha
recently the government of India
reintegrated Kashmir Jammu Kashmir in
India first time in seventy years
after independence Jammu Kashmir has been
properly treated with the
and subscribe to Radhe Day
status
and is to use
it 4 inches up statement is to
westward things to be minute happened
around world trade Gonda up
area card and seizure response dot
that the team milk symptoms response in
India
which is that 560 eastern states of India
c whatsapp uninstall northern states
of India
hain another 500 India in  Southern states
are well
settled activities happening now
that a positive energy is happening sleep se
activities being orchestrated by all of us
a bright future tense mat yaar bus lagi aur
been controlled by certain death and
health enhancing sims pair integration of
kashmir all the big challenges russia to india
solvent innovative 20 2009 posted by
of scientific
officer using indian citizens for any
subject be what is the
condition of interference and
colonialism
ek bhar so called great game inse
tubelight great game which was tough contest
between
philosophy umpire in british umpire and
objectives of india the british rule in
india and world peace
and should be placed in the central asian
countries have access to the
content on a
few have deposited kindly supported
democratic and controlled dharma
plunder se vriddhi ke use se different places unki
family update you give water vayu
awards and good candidate from
without from outside India remember see what happen
in collector baitha hoon what
exactly is that is that is what is
whatsapp of
parts of
speech in
to-do list
play
plane mode setting famous and fennel flight do end
crisis in friend famous
mysterious loose elections of events appear on i
isko lax jab
pimples means look at all these will warson
objectionable africa just your suicide
interference wise details to where is come to
power in africa pure installed
sports bike quarter inch towers
subscribe continuing colony laser miss you know where to look into it can
recognize
symptoms will see everywhere is
inside india
inside a
pune
mili then they want to be our
day-to-day
life our
country
a
democratic country se ho to father is
colony mein hawassaapna cord time it's
high time
mission protect india rise up candidate
time hai
this boxing
that with appearance how did not come with
appearance  Now dinosaurs Major Ali and the basis
of skeletal structure housed Vinod Saif
Quite as valid as saying this
week is Vriksha constructed dinosaurs look like
based on the skeletons up I have
discovered so we back later this
reconstruction Sudhir
and you
a modern
look
structure of the
giver simple drawing of the return of the
day
happy
birthday to you your opinion degeneration software
cute
skeleton give very different impression of
our day like
subscribe and share
9th may big eyes nose
you will be
different for elections will be
different for the
time
third point is
that today they have real eyes date
almost and dinosaurs handsfree eyes can you
believe three factors which
discoveries in celebs subscribe to China
Daily do
n't forget to subscribe to Now to Different Worlds channel
thumbs up
subscribe for like skin
most likely it must be in
accord with others
that I will  no how much for city typically ceo vikram
dinosaur affairs best on tight
fitting skin rash
show which give this you will get appearance me
also de and shroff in some cases under big
limit soberon no bro
nov18 able to find for sacrifice of
animals should begin to be defined
members for research f5 that 20% handsfree
amazon education final years but look and
birds they can not a good idea to
demonstrate slim look like 64 bit for
badole little success quite different from
mother board excited life mother gives no
indication of v reconstruction not been very much
awaited morning vishuddha chakra and
construction white source 20 not been
observed more than samsung
instead it tu ab an dinosaur dinosaur dinosaur
dinosaur still love among 800
urs but that
person's
robbers
ball
subscribe
possibly be more
ok this fast
food
and drug administration
of people
from  Pataliputra
develop more your enemy look what you have
observed is crouch
that Chandragupta Maurya emperor of India has
no time to look into the date today from
villages and towns and cities
his duty objective long-term security
difficulty office empire
look at the big picture temple temple tended to every
day and WhatsApp to
point administrators level jobs for
not going to my
channel
subscribe to a
souvenir rice north-west it simply
Gandu back to point regional
administrators and state province level
the city Birbal town level village level gram
panchayat lovely and all the right you need at
chairs for division of labour and every
country
[music]
beauty but all of you
against the legends on dum
that dimple was doing anything without express
approval
polysyllable approval of temperature
in vidmate notice amazon and words i went to impose ban
on system did
not make  decisions on their and
implicated in implementing policies
inside on
understand the
policy withdrawal inside top o
hello friends implement dost policies
record note protein vitamin e one ok
my status guddu gram flour use this language
thumb introduce release number has base
system of education in the different urine you know it
120 b office had to it was
strong centralized
structure and brilliant example of
empire wise and widely
read
and administration and administrative
structure
governor sub-continent size has that in
today's cases the same thing dham upanishad
cigarette train time of kumar gupta chandra gupta
samudra gupta rida majhu people insaan
aapko delegate responsibility to our people
for governance but everybody to be used to predict that
rate policies paper has set
nomadic tribes come independence day
pal tule day kal
morning cigarette lawyers state subject
state will set the tone policies  in everything in the
centre current affair what nonsense this
India is no longer united as a single
civilization with his
every state cow protection and
Assam policy in the centre closed state ke andar policy
address on vim
that central zone to that difficult for the country but
some states are not doing any
specific artist button stage par dabish di
but samota is that but
dresses
with something I have never died in the time
for great emperors never humble hai 10
December 15
2009 2013 comment
subscribe
subscribe to Bank of India
very strong central government
for debate now crotch length and breadth of
observation deck at what India needs we are the
Chinese in johny johny since India too much
difficulty in everything can
run on
specific
subscribe
move away from the system has been imposed upon the
system date of the Times of India needs
scientist Karan Shesh I think Vikram the
greatest of all time goat Congress
activists  Khan Amla ke andar Singh this
Kanishka Samudragupta Pauravas Chandreshwar
Giri Technical Institute Generals
Bade Hai Fuel Marshal Private Jobs Tips
Liquid Liner Are you the
member of civilization
and Kanishka PM of all of India and
India
Samudragupta Emperor Chandragupta Maurya
Rajendra Yadav Great Are you you are the
most valuable person Indian
civilization in your life Easier Tags Page
9 Tags Page 10
Click Please Do You Want To See A
Right Now Things When You Are In Military
Camp In Your Desire But Not Participate
Give Or Debt The Question Why You Should Also Be Very Often That
You Issue This
And Women Soldiers In To Forms They Will Have To
Order People Don't See Side In
Vitamin
Y0 Soldiers Who Believe In God And Asked This
Question On
Abe So To-Do List You To Understand And
Principles On
I One Sheet To Be A Great General You Need The
Respect  Woman you need love and affection
and
respect woman to
death over
country needs
admission in do you know it back
discharge will help and country
is the general issues should respect of
subscribe
the question
of
class 10th
enemy chandra gupta and young young boy his
father was here and sanjay kumar gupta
hitesh and during his father and drop
this grade grade waves in north
node
they were invented in india was a
boy took
charge of his father's army personnel
in
forbes hai
ghar par hi participated in this battle
sports nli sports live online again
and again and again in his rude toe
everybody is not the robot
boy
smart boy
is the the the nothing left to
improve is dedication
civilization
[music]
Video then
subscribe to the Page if you liked The
Video
then
subscribe to
the Page
which period like time of the time in only be
invisible tourist status the
richest temples in which state has not  been
requesting you your word is low and every
citizen should not enter
definition
subscribe no longer participated in the
world channel must
subscribe
participate in the
great wall street for the great hemchandra
vikramaditya
last hindu emperor of india it back on quick no longer root
panchavati embroidery
important what to do command universal
life
is a
delegation of the nation of
observation
loot
man who will
follow you anywhere on ho gaya
and yashwant say yes vote leadership
qualities mast portion have in order to
lead a node tilak india with such diversity
and problems of present-day scene are you once again
Ujjain back to back to the times
of the great
kings eleven punjab india chandragupta
maurya ep 124 clock lord rama when
lord krishna the great and craft room
and confy awards winners name and others like this and
chandragupta maurya kanishka
great relief provided free speed mango
that the great  Gupta Emperors Browser
Rajendra Chola I want to regret Shivaji
Maharaj right what leadership quality he has with his wide lives in their
careers a person with
leadership quality and
given
no country
first of all you need to know what is that
such machine Nishan video it's all about
power
chicken father he man of the world youth
power all they want to
lead a single lineage want to be addicted to enter
your life to the service
of the nation it first come to power at come to
power without understanding the true nature
of power power is the great ministry of
power is the greatest ministry issues can you
understand the mystery if you know start understand what both of you
understand through the nature of what prevents power
rangers power comes from where are
you the
least powerful violators the prime
minister has been prime minister and become
completely powerless
that if in office but he will not be in power a
power is something and central
power structures
star extra electronic
Suggestion for
power really understand how to
use it that it
understand power of service power
of discipline and power power hundred twenty good
quality
complete transparency and integrity
possible that interests you thank you intend to be in
trouble
subscribe to the people international picture
window contents of 68th
that rohit dasha hi titli khushal hue is
note family unmarried ki new remix
subscribe must must understand what is going to and the things
you do
and leadership very different from what a
joke is
now I have said that is not a leader is on something
and leadership quality seeds and
managing people before
taking a bunch of technology and
pulind celebration on
leadership attitude and this boot service
leader is not boss boss is not under start
from 24th august understanding will
eventually
that d booster for 10th
lot iss
kinda gyaan necessary whatsapp
notification for government want you checked
location he next  Leaders ignore
electronics and see the most patients
from government on who is
the form of government in various opportunism a
rapidly in real time in two not just made rapid like
truth improvement and
forest in the
last 20 century has been the fastest and
implement the best all the best
option for government a
government which
makes informed decisions made in real-time
blog click
implement a very
good
information
in long-term interest that is the best
option for government
jobs
in up to
last 9 democratic movements good
making decisions right decisions in parties
international stars have nothing against them matters
not the form of government for a
long-term
security in prosperity and the
only thing that
I drink holding elections once every few years hinders
how many Twenty20 teams did I
work for in years s Deoria Border
Security Force approximately 55-decimal
addition when you have elections elections
looming
Looming in front of you you know it is pay
different
electoral politics
impose restrictions on
you want to see the country and you have to make your own you have to win
elections but will fight
with you cannot win
elections unless you PL
's vow that do not
understand the real Karam Ali dar
good new leader has to make a
difference he has hard earned
popular choice
to play the short Ronit will have a long way in the
long run
is pain in love
you to
make  Up Sid
Person Ne Shyam Ji Angry Birds Decision
Dhoom 1 Litre Pani Popular Date Mix Leaders
News Election
2012 To-Do List Politics Politics Key
Cars On Its Own
Country
Subscribe
If You Form A Government Government Has Been
Very Different From A Ki Is
Age Me Bhi 1025 Cigarette Me Bhi China
Choli The World Will Revert Back
To Rumor Imperial System Private
Security Sinus In Russia To Western
System Is Not Arise System Lost
Subscribe Please Please
The
Duty Rava Idli
Sandwich
Subscribe Button
And System System Crumbling Stairs To Of This
Country
Progress On That
You Should Also Choose Should Be Increased Number Of
Items In India Considering A Large Number
Of Youth Award To Per Civil Engineering
And Improve The Quality Of Existence It Was
In India Since Of UID Number
Per Send Episode 185 Is The Oldest Website Per
Option Has To Any Sentence On
Yo Yo 2nd Stop This  it would once you will see
the devil now million dollar washrooms
million dollar conference rooms in the
recruitment
instrumentation in recent years old
there made dishes wrong way beginners
administrators and brock lesnar fight is
powder get and even thoshe subjective senior
army hok
yuvraj
study saath just mediocre bhi iodine top
hundred years old water will change its
benefits of oil change
dowry run with two in maybe right leadership this place in which it is a
possibility to improve the quality of it
but change but very few minutes
system in the country is widely there is
one IIT and every district in
India on
ajay devgan starring engineer location of the
country has earned it never defeat at least one which
state in india
every day
ok kha lo
[music] is
deep in modern science you review and
tourism boss-4's father in law asaf economic
times wensday dismissed rice flour most
judge 19th  material worlds case
filed oregano agreed
not to exist only the material
world world exists in the
objective of life enjoy your and your
physical body the physical life in these sells it is
possible in obscene scenes philosophy
science says nothing but environment science
award of mines are not you to know what
your life is but science says something about the
morality in the field of science all about that without
understanding
diya beads
tomato juice about object bulb
in films not
intact data interpretation of statutes
constipation on seams to be in love you to make of
idioms and logic of
superficial level without
morality is
that justice and perspective of the world
with
interview how to love you live in a certain way
make cake without egg foundation
is but not done sanjay ki nikli tourism books
name and
custom of offering
various schools for science in
india and his aid
409 Subscribe
Subscribe
Indian civilization and different schools
of thought for the day of
judgment simply amazing when a
person appears in a
cogent judgment ok ok
different hai
meanwhile political politics of vote for
india upcoming up election
vote for political party in your opinion
in your assessment investment
political parties appeal
124 terminal at his confessional interest for
most here remind our party but will
develop the state of up for the better economically financially
culturally it will impose better law and
order condition it has 225 the past history
for corrupt leaders will improve the law
order that will give people law and justice
at will
that you
improve the economic constipation state
that and well
you will bring the state back to its former glory which
political party which will
contact you can be used
to various political parties in the
country on
mode on ribbon last question
playlist is something about your personal
life
please subscribe my channel
subscribe button
30.70 on star system should learn
from your system
object swallow
that you mix in assam list and wait for the
right time final race sufficient
technological development at which time my
my dance class to send back that
to my people and my star system second
number 2017 happened
national people and destroyed during it's just
joking all the
great fun with questions please coming tomorrow tomorrow will
live session division
more
wish you very very good night bye I love you